const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'Prior to having their name changed to the Houston Astros, this team was known as the',
    answers: [
      'Houston Rockets',
      'Houston Colt .45s',
      'Houston Comets',
      'Houston Heat'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Houston Colt .45s'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which year did the Astros win their first and only National League Pennant?',
    answers: [
      '2017',
      '2004',
      '1994',
      '2005'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '2005'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the Astros manager when they won their first and only National League Pennant?',
    answers: [
      'Phil Garner',
      'AJ Hinch',
      'Milo Hamilton',
      'Alex Cora'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Phil Garner'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Astros player was inducted into the Hall of Fame in 2015, had over 3000 career hits, and was a 4x Golden Glove Winner, who is he?',
    answers: [
      'Jose Altuve',
      'Roger Clemens',
      'Craig Biggio',
      'Jeff Bagwell'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Craig Biggio'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Astros player hit 5 home runs during the World Series, and was a World Series MVP, who is he?',
    answers: [
      'Jose Altuve',
      'Carlos Correa',
      'Lance Berkman',
      'George Springer'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'George Springer'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which year did the Astros win their first ever World Series Championship?',
    answers: [
      '2005',
      '2017',
      '2016',
      '1994'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '2017'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Astros player won the American League MVP award in 2017, who is he?',
    answers: [
      'Jeff Bagwell',
      'Yuli Gurriel',
      'Jose Altuve',
      'George Springer'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Jose Altuve'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Astros player won the National League MVP award in 1994, who is he?',
    answers: [
      'Jeff Bagwell',
      'Craig Biggio',
      'Jose Altuve',
      'Jose Lima'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Jeff Bagwell'
  },
  {
    question: 'This stadium was named an 8th Wonder of the World and housed the Astros until the year 2000, what was it called?',
    answers: [
      'The Summit',
      'The Astrodome',
      'Colt Stadium',
      'Minute Maid Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Astrodome'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the Astros manager when they won their first ever World Series Championship',
    answers: [
      'AJ Hinch',
      'Alex Cora',
      'Phil Garner',
      'Marwin Gonzales'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'AJ Hinch'
  },
];